mindarc.com.au 2019-03-21

# MindArc Privacy Policy - MindArc Digital

**Privacy Policy**

MindArc recognises that your personal information is important to you and share your concerns about how information is collected, used and shared. We are committed to safeguarding your personal information and will always handle your personal information securely and carefully.

We are committed to complying with all applicable Australian Privacy Laws and General Data Protection Regulations and ensure that our staff are aware of their obligations. The following should give you a greater understanding on how we collect and use customer information.

**Why we collect information**

_We collect information for a few reasons including:_

To deliver services to you via email or phone  
To complete transactions with you or on your behalf  
To better understand your requirements and preferences  
To Improve our service

**How we collect this information**

_We collect information in a few ways:_

When you order services online.  
If you complete one of our surveys or respond to requests for information as part of a promotion.  
If you submit a request for information via our website.

**What we collect**

The personal information we may collect is in most cases supplied by you when you place an enquiry or provide feedback to us. Name, address, company, phone number, e-mail address, current website and transaction information.

**Who we may share your information with**

We never share your personal data with third party marketing providers. You information will be stored and managed by our team in a secure database. We may disclose personal information to government authorities as required by law. In these circumstances, we will ensure that these third parties undertake to protect your privacy.

If you would like to access or update your personal information, write to us via email, post or via telephone. We prefer to receive written requests as in many cases this assists us to verify your identity.

**Direct marketing**

If you receive marketing offers from us and do not wish to receive them in the future, please let us know, or use the link in the email footer to immediately unsubscribe.

**Terms and conditions**

Acceptance of Terms –  
When you access this web site, you acknowledge that you have read and agree to abide by the terms described below.

While MindArc attempts to provide accurate information on this Web site, it assumes no responsibility for accuracy. MindArc may change the information on the site, or the products mentioned, at any time without notice.

Copyright –  
The entire website of MindArc is the sole property of MindArc Pty Ltd and it is protected under applicable copyrights.

Under no circumstances may the site be reproduced, re-used or redistributed for any purposes whatsoever without written permission from the management of MindArc.
